//creating an array and passing the number,questions,options and answers
let questions=[
    {
        numb:1,
        question:" Artificial Intelligence is about_____.",
        answer:"Making a machine Intelligent",
        options:[
            "Playing a game on Computer",
            "Making a machine Intelligent",
            "Programming on Machine with your Own Intelligence",
            "Putting your intelligence in Machine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:" Who is known as the -Father of AI?",
        answer:"John McCarthy",
        options:[
            "Fisher Ada",
            "Alan Turing ",
            "John McCarthy ",
            "Allen Newell "
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"Select the most appropriate situation for that a blind search can be used.",
        answer:"Small Search Space",
        options:[
            "Real-life situation",
            "Small Search Space",
            "Complex game",
            "All of the above"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:" The application/applications of Artificial Intelligence is/are",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options:[
            "Expert Systems",
            "Gaming",
            "Vision Systems",
            "All of the above"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"Among the given options, which search algorithm requires less memory?",
        answer:"Depth First Search",
        options:[
            "Optimal Search",
            "Depth First Search",
            "Breadth-First Search",
            "Linear Search"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
        answer:"Perl",
        options:[
            "LISP",
            "PROLOG",
            "Python",
            " Perl"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"The component of an Expert system is_________.",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options:[
            "Knowledge Base",
            "Inference Engine",
            "User Interface",
            "All of the above"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Which algorithm is used in the Game tree to make decisions of Win/Lose?",
        answer:"Min/Max Algorithm",
        options:[
            "Heuristic Search Algorithm",
            "DFS/BFS algorithm",
            "Greedy Search Algorithm",
            "Min/Max Algorithm"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"The available ways to solve a problem of state-space-search.",
        answer:"2",
        options:[
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"An AI agent perceives and acts upon the environment using___.",
        answer:"Both a and c.",
        options:[
            "Sensors",
            "Perceiver",
            "Actuators",
            "Both a and c."
        ] 
    },
    

]